I'm going, Nanamin.
You can't.
I already explained why this morning.
If a veil has been cast,
there's a strong likelihood he's both
alive and at Satozakura High School.
I'll be back soon.
Please wait there, Itadori-kun.
It's probably pointless to ask him that.
You heard why, so I'll leave
the rest of this to you, Ino-kun.
Huh?!
Is there a problem with that?
Well, the number of them...
There's a lot.
And they're all humans, right?
I wouldn't mind taking on the recommendation
to make you a grade 1 jujutsu sorcerer.
Let's get this done, baby! Yeah!
Please step aside, Ijichi-san.
Our job is to help others.
That includes those who are
still students, like yourself.
I won't make any more mistakes.
You must not go, Itadori-kun.
Sorry, Ijichi-san.
What are you doing, Junpei?!
Stay out of this, jujutsu sorcerer.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Episode 12:  To You, Someday
Moon Dregs!
A jellyfish shikigami?
Blunt attacks won't work
when he's inside it?
I'll say it one more time.
Stay out of this, jujutsu sorcerer!
It's none of your business!
That's not something you get to decide!
What's the point of indiscriminate salvation?
Don't mistake the value of a life!
People pretend their
emotions are everything,
but the heart is just the
metabolism of the soul.
It's all a delusion!
Don't restrict me with rules
that are based on a delusion.
No one has the right to stop anyone
from taking what lives they can.
Just sleep over there.
There's something I have to go back and do.
Your cursed technique is poison.
You produce poison from cursed energy
and make your shikigami
secrete it from its tentacles.
You'll learn to control
the size and strength of your shikigami,
as well as the potency of your poison.
A normal jujutsu sorcerer would
need some time to grasp it,
but I'll teach you the sensation,
so you'll be able to fight right away.
Junpei, you have talent.
Who are you making excuses for?
Why?
Why won't Moon Dregs' poison work on him?
Why are you getting in my way?
Why?!
He's in the air! He can't move!
No... if there's a chance to crush him,
it's right before he lands!
Junpei, I don't understand...
a damn thing you're saying!
You can string together
whatever logic you want.
When facing shikigami users,
strike the sorcerer directly.
You're just trying...
to convince yourself you're in the right!
I don't know what your motive is.
I'm sure you have a reason for doing this.
But is it really worth
throwing away that life you have?
The human heart is a delusion?
Can you say that in front of her?!
People don't have hearts.
You're still—
They don't!
Otherwise...
That would mean people cursed me
and my mom with those hearts!
That would just be too much...
I wouldn't know what is right
or what is wrong anymore...
Why didn't you dodge it?
Sorry.
I said a lot of self-important stuff
without understanding anything.
Tell me what happened.
I swear I won't curse you anymore.
So please.
No way... Your mom...
Junpei, come to Jujutsu Tech.
There are lots of crazy strong teachers
and reliable friends there.
If we all work together,
I'm sure we can find
whoever cursed your mom.
Then you can make sure they get their due!
Let's fight together!
Who are you?
Who is that?
A person?
Nice to meet you...
No, this feels like...
...vessel of Sukuna.
Mahito-san, wait!
Am I an idiot?!
A human-shaped cursed spirit
with a patchwork face!
This is exactly what
Nanamin said would happen!
Junpei, run!
I don't know what
relationship you have with him,
but right now, just run!
Please!
Itadori-kun, please calm down!
Mahito-san's not a bad person...
Bad... person...
You know, Junpei, you've got
a good head on your shoulders.
But sometimes deliberation can lead
to worse foolishness than imprudence.
You're a stereotypical case of that!
You're almost as foolish as
those people you call fools yourself.
That's why you'll die.
Idle Transfiguration.
Now, time for round two.
Junpei...
Junpei!
Get a hold of yourself!
I'll heal you right now!
Sukuna!
What?
I'll do anything!
You can do anything you want with me!
So heal Junpei like you did
when you restored my heart!
I refuse!
Damn you...
Good.
He's completely forgotten about that pact.
How very amusing!
You'd offer up your pride,
your future, your everything,
to try to rely on me...
And you can't save anything!
He refused the pact?
The shape of one's soul isn't something that
reverse cursed techniques could deal with...
Maybe healing others is beyond him?
Pathetic!
You couldn't be more pathetic, brat!
Though, what I'm after is what comes next,
so I guess this is fine.
Oh, that's right.
At the end of the day,
these two are both
curses.
Yuuji...
Why?
Oh, dead already?
I suppose I was kind of rough
when I changed his shape.
Guess that's how it goes.
That was an unusual blow.
Interesting!
Too bad, though.
That won't work. So long
as I maintain the shape of my—
What's going on?!
He struck the shape of my soul, as well?
That's right!
Itadori Yuuji's a vessel.
His body constantly houses another
soul in addition to his own.
So naturally...
You're aware...
of the outline of your soul?
The next words that spilled from my lips
came from so deep within
my gut that it nearly made
all the things I've ever said feel like a lie.
I will kill you!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Don't you mean you'll
"exorcise" me, jujutsu sorcerer?
Itadori Yuuji isn't concerned
with his own life.
Getou forbade me from forcing him
into an external pact using hostages.
So if he can't kill a foe he hates
so much that he longs to kill them,
he'll probably turn to Sukuna.
If Junpei isn't enough,
I'd just need to transform every
student, one by one, before his eyes.
That would lead Itadori Yuuji to negotiate
and forge a pact with Sukuna
while he's full of hatred for self-interest.
If that also improved the chances of
Sukuna joining our side, all the better.
Though, all of that presumes
that I'm stronger than him.
So why did he have to be
my natural enemy?
He keeps changing his damn shape so much!
Would it be better to stop thinking of
combos that start with holds and throws?
Now that I know his attacks work on me,
changing my shape and making
his target bigger is a bad idea.
In that case...
Even if it takes a hundred or a thousand times,
I'll keep pounding him
into a pulp!
I'll use a shape more honed toward murder,
with more inspiration for murder,
and manifest it!
You can't keep stretching forever!
Most people would let go, you know.
Spreading my shape too much causes it
to lose strength and maneuverability.
You can't beat me.
Swap out already...
with Sukuna.
Idle Transfiguration.
You dare touch my soul?
Since we both heartily ridiculed
that brat together,
I'll allow it once.
There won't be a second time.
Know your place,
fool.
I'm not swapping out.
I already told you...
I will kill you.
Huh?
Nanamin!
I'll lecture you later.
Tell me the situation.
I couldn't save two people.
It's always others first?
Explain your physical state first.
I'm fine.
Though I'm full of holes.
That's not fine.
Also, everyone from this school
is unconscious in the gym.
Hey, you're alive and well, 7:3 sorcerer!
Glad to see we both survived.
Shall we share a hug,
in celebration of our reunion?
Itadori-kun, why is his nose bleeding?
Huh? I punched him.
When?
At the start of our fight.
Did his hand touch you?
Yeah.
My attacks won't work on him.
Huh?!
What?! Why?!
I'll explain while I'm lecturing you.
One, his technique doesn't
work on Itadori-kun,
or two, there's some reason
he won't kill Itadori-kun.
Either way, that's good for us.
However, I can halt his movements.
Once we've both created an opening,
we'll shower him with blows.
We'll make sure to exorcise him here.
Yeah!
Juju Stroll
Episode 13:
Tomorrow